<resources>

    <!-- general -->
    <string name="app_name">Average data usage widget</string>
    <string name="txt_title_info">Information:</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_info">This is a small widget utility to show the data plan usage with a \'constant\' usage bar. Useful to know if you are above or below the \'constant\' data usage (if you consume the same data every second).  \nApp created by TrianguloY (<a href="mailto:correo--correo+appCDUW@hotmail.com?Subject=Continous data usage">email</a>)\n\nWidget description:  \n- The upper bar is the optimal continuous usage: 0 at the start of the period, half at the middle of the period, full at the end.   \n- The bottom bar is your current usage. If the bottom bar is less than the upper bar then at that rate you will have data unused. If it is more then you will probably surpass it.  \n- Click the right button of the widget to open android usage settings, click anywhere else to manually update it (it updates automatically).</string>


    <!-- permissions -->
    <string name="txt_title_permissions">Permissions:</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_permission_phoneState">READ_PHONE_STATE:\nPermission needed to get the <a href="https://developer.android.com/reference/android/telephony/TelephonyManager.html#getSubscriberId()">device identificator</a>. No other data is retrieved nor used. Click the button below to give the permission if necessary.</string>
    <string name="btn_permission_phoneState">Ask permission</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_permission_usageStats">PACKAGE_USAGE_STATS:\nPermission needed to get the current usage from the <a href="https://developer.android.com/reference/android/app/usage/NetworkStatsManager.html#querySummaryForDevice(int,%20java.lang.String,%20long,%20long)">usage service</a>. No other data is retrieved nor used. If required click the button below, select this app and enable the permission.</string>
    <string name="btn_permission_usageStats">Usage Stats settings</string>
    <string name="txt_permissionGranted">Permission granted</string>
    <string name="txt_permissionsNeeded">Permission needed</string>
    <string name="txt_error_noPermisionState">Error while getting permission state</string>


    <!-- settings -->
    <string name="txt_title_settings">Settings:</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_setting_totalData">Total data: usage to show in the upper bar when totally filled. Normally your data plan limit. In megabytes (MB)</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_setting_firstDay">First day of period: when to start counting usage (day of month)</string>
    <string name="txt_desc_setting_altConv">Alternate conversion: Check this if data usage shown is always less than real usage returned by your company app. [Technical details: uses 1000 instead of 1024 to convert from bytes to megabytes]</string>
    <string name="chkbx_setting_altConv">Use alternate MB conversion</string>


    <!-- widget -->
    <string name="txt_widget_unloaded">-loading-</string>
    <string name="txt_widget_noPermission">Permission missing</string>
    <string name="txt_widget_errorQuering">Error querying data</string>
    <string name="txt_widget_errorService">Service unavailable</string>
    <string name="toast_currentUsage">Your current usage correspond to date:\n%s\n(%s)</string>

</resources>
